>> Jem Young: 在容器和常规负载均衡上的最后一部分
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And the last section on
containers and general load balancing
引擎 x 正在调整这些高级的部署。
engine x tweaking this advanced
things is deployments.
我们讨论了编排作为部署容器的方法。
We talked about orchestration as
a way of deploying containers.
但如果我们不使用微型服务和容器
But if we weren't using micro services and
containers,
如何更快地部署 20 台服务器?
what's a faster way of
deploying 20 servers?
我不想让杰姆 - 扬年轻的
I don't necessarily wanna go
through Jem Young's full stack for
前端课程，然后我就会复制我的 SSH 密钥。
front end course and
be like then I copy my SSH key over.
然后我想运行所有这些脚本来安装所有内容。
And then I wanna run all these
scripts to install everything.
每次 20 次你都得这么做
You have to do that every time 20 times.
那是不可伸缩的
That's not scalable.
幸运的是，存在一些工具，您可以设置配置脚本。
Fortunately, there are tools out there
that you set up a configuration scripts.
你给它一些资源和一些服务器 IP 你可以设置上百个
And you give it some resources and some
server IPs and you can set up hundreds or
数以千计的服务器。
thousands of servers at once.
因此，更流行的工具是 " 流浪汉 " ， " 傀儡 " 或 " 厨师 " 。
So the more popular tools to be answerable
vagrant and puppet or chef is another one.
这些非常流行的工具用于旋转 20 台服务器
These are really popular tools for
spinning up 20 servers are taking down
20 台服务器，数百台服务器和数千台服务器。
20 servers, hundreds servers,
and thousands of servers.
当你得到好的时候你就会把我们之前做的一切都带走
When you get really good, you'll just
take everything that we did earlier and
你把它放到剧本里然后每次都把它滚出去
you put it in the scripts and then you
just roll that out every single time.
还记得那天结束的时候
And because remember,
at the end of the day,
最棒的工程师才是最棒的
the best engineers are the laziest ones.
因此，如果您可以将所有重复的工作脚本用于配置引擎 x 和
So if you can script all that repeated
work that we did configuring engine x and
所有这些都变成了简单的剧本只会让你的生活变得很简单
all these things into one simple scripts,
that just makes your life much,
更容易
much easier.